Matango
This is the psychiatric ward .
Yes , I know that .
And you think that I 'm insane .
Don 't you ?
All of my friends died .
Every one of them .
No ! I 'm the one who died .
It 's true . They 're alive !
Then you want to know why they didn 't return , don 't you ?
I don 't want to tell you the story .
It would only convince you that I really am insane .
Oh , it 's wonderful out here .
We 've left everything behind .
Everything ?
I mean everything that 's horrible in Tokyo .
You shouldn 't talk that way , you know .
Why not ?
Tokyo 's a great city , and it 's full of life .
Everything in it 's important .
Is that right ?
Hey , my manuscript !
Hey , Yoshida !
Why don 't you stop working .
Dammit .
This is gonna be my best book .
You always say that .
What ? I 'll get you ...
Hey , hey ...
I 'll remember that .
- First time at sea , huh ? - Yeah .
Too bad !
I really don 't think she 's enjoying it .
- Hey , it 's my first time too . - Yeah , but you know how to live .
She doesn 't .
You know , she won 't even let her boyfriend kiss her .
- I wonder who 's normal . - Yeah .
- What 's the matter . - Why .
- Do you feel sick ? - Uh-uh .
I 'm sorry about this .
I don 't know how to act with them .
Ah , they 're a nice bunch of guys .
This is a great opportunity for you .
Don 't be afraid .
Okay .
Come on , Koyama , put your work away , huh .
She 's sure easy on the eyes on , huh ?
Yeah , really nice .
So she 's Mami ...
radio and television 's first lady of song .
She single , or married ?
- Not exactly . - Huh ?
Oh , she 's somebody 's mistress , then ?
For now , let 's drink .
Just a second .
This drink is very significant .
At this moment ...
We 're completely free from all the problems of the man .
From each difficulty .
- So we should ... - There you go again .
Aren 't all of us here part of humanity .
Sure , but I think we 're basically different from the general run of people .
- I better check the wind . - Hey , wait a minute .
I got work to do . I 'm the skipper .
Well , let 's drink to Akiko , shall we ? Good luck .
To your health .
Oh boy , we can expect some rough seas tonight .
- Radio , huh ? - Yeah .
There 's a low pressure area west of Kyushu .
I thought we 'd have ideal weather today .
We should turn back .
That 's not up to me .
You know , skipper , they 're strange people .
They got more money than brains .
They 're more like reckless children .
They 'll be children no matter how old they get .
A bunch of parasites sponging off people !
But that happens to be the way world .
Look , if you don 't have confidence in yourself , then I 'll take over .
Ahh , I 'm just telling you what I think .
Listen here , confidence is very important .
Personally , I 'd like to keep sailing as we planned .
It 'll be a lotta fun if we have some rough weather , won 't it ?
Don 't forget about the 2 women .
Just don 't worry about me , I 'll be all right .
How ' bout you ?
I 'll be all right .
Yeah , yeah , we 'll be okay .
I paid a lot of money for this yacht , and I think it 'll weather any storm we hit .
Hey , captain . Captain , come here !
- What is it ? ! - Look !
Hey , the jib !
Everybody on deck !
Come on , let 's go .
- Get that sail down ! - Right !
Help me out !
Get it !
Hurry !
Now , don 't worry .
Why , this yacht will never sink .
Remember what Kasai said ?
That it cost him a lot of money .
You know how much it cost ?
Forty million yen !
He must be crazy .
But then ...
I 'm going to get to go to Europe on it this fall .
Paris .
Rome .
Vienna !
Everywhere .
I 'm gonna sing everywhere .
- I 'll keep it steady ! - Okay !
I 'm going below !
How is it ?
Oh , we 'll be all right .
You must be frightened .
Sorry . You feel sick ?
- Yes . - Oh ...
Well , we better turn back then .
Hurry up , now !
Take her down !
Hey , you 're a professor of psychology , aren 't ya ?
Yeah !
Did you know ...
if you threaten a girl
then pretend to be sympathetic to her , she 'll fall for you immediately ?
That 's the way you writers think .
That 's not psychology !
Hey , you relieve Murai !
Okay !
- Okay , I 'll get it . - All right .
Are you all right ?
Don 't worry .
We 'll be okay .
Kasai , the engine , start it !
The anchor ! The anchor !
- Drop it ! - Right !
The mast is gone ! Get below ! Everybody !
Get below ! Go on !
Definitely , the yacht will never sink , I 'm sure of it !
Hey , the radio , it 's smashed !
Hey , Sakuta , the engines no good , it won 't start !
And it 's all your fault that we 're in trouble now !
What 's that ?
- Hey , where 's Yoshida ? - Huh ?
What 's he doing ?
Dammit !
Yoshida !
He 's okay !
Hold on .
Come on .
Come on . Get him below !
Are you all right ?
Yeah .
Are you hurt ?
Yoshida , Yoshida !
Well , it 's all over .
We can only hope they 'll start a search for us .
I think they will , don 't you ?
I think so .
Are we drifting ?
Yeah .
To the south .
The south .
Where are-where are we now ?
The direction finder is damaged .
We 're helpless ?
That 's right .
But ...
youâ   re the skipper , so you ...
Skipper ?
Yeah , skipper .
Even on the yacht , you had to give the orders !
You , had to play skipper !
Isn 't there anything we can do ?
Hey .
Don 't waste the battery .
Save it until the news comes on .
It 's on now .
The yacht was reported missing after the heavy storm .
The 7 people , believed on board , have been identified as ...
Masafumi Kasai , owner of the yacht , and president of the Kasai-Sankyo Company .
Etsuro Yoshida , famous mystery writer .
Mami Sekiguchi , radio and television star .
Kenji Murai , assistant professor of psychology at Jinan University .
Akiko Soma , a student at the university .
Sakuta , the skipper of the yacht , and a sailor , Senzo Koyama .
Because Mr. Sakuta is an experienced yachtsman ,
he placed 5th in last year 's successful yacht race ,
the Marine Security Office believes the yacht may have survived the storm .
That is the end of the news bulletin , the next one 's on the coming hour .
Here now , is the weather report for the next ...
Well , I guess the battery 's dead .
A ship .
Hey !
Look out !
What is it ?
Hey .
Yoshida ! Yoshida !
Yoshida !
Wake up .
Hey .
When is this fog gonna break up , aye ?
How much water 's left ?
Ah , shut up .
You 'll wear yourself out gabbing .
My head feels funny .
What 's gonna to happen to me ?
Huh .
What 's up .
Nothing .
Aw , stop that !
Everyone knows .
All of them know what you 're after .
They know why you didn 't want to go back when the weather got worse .
No wonder a woman 's taboo on a ship .
It 's certainly not because the gods became jealous of ' em .
It 's really because all the men on the ship start to ...
lose their heads .
It 's-it 's land !
It 's land !
Lan ...
It 's-it 's an island !
It 's an island !
Land !
What ?
Hey ! Come on !
Look .
Is that Japan ?
I think it might be the Bonin islands .
Well , is it deserted ?
We need some food first .
Then we can look around the island .
Watch the branch .
It 's getting foggy .
Better find something very soon , while we can still see .
- Hey , where are we going ? - Huh ?
You don 't have to come if you don 't want to .
Fine ... let 's go . Come on .
Here , take my hand .
What is it ?
Water !
Huh ?
It sounds like water !
Oh .
Water .
Hey !
There 's water here !
Hey , it 's water . Come on !
Come on .
Those rocks .
It 's not deserted .
- Huh ? - Somebody arranged those rocks .
Yeah .
Hey , maybe we should go back .
There seems to be a trail .
What ?
Let 's go across the island .
There might be some houses over there .
Hey .
Are we going up there ?
Watch your step here .
We 're on the edge of a cliff .
Look at that .
It 's a ship .
Hey , let 's go down there .
Hold my hand . Come on .
Hey !
Hold it !
It 's only a wreck .
Look at at .
That sails are rotten .
It 's probably been stranded over a year ago .
Let 's take a look anyway .
There might be somebody on board .
Hey , you gonna look , huh ?
What a disgusting sight .
Won 't be anything there but some rotten bodies .
Don 't say that .
I 'll wait here .
They would have eaten all their food before they died .
Yoshida .
You girls wait here for us , we 'll go take a look .
- Come on then . - Yeah .
Sure looks beaten up .
Somebody could be living on it .
What happened ?
The steps are slimy .
It 's fungus .
Nobody here .
It 's weird .
Umm .
It 's thick with fungus .
What 's that ?
What the hell are you doing ?
Not a damn bit of food anyway .
Let 's go up and find them .
I don 't like waiting here .
Looks like a water pump .
Hey , a Geiger counter .
Some kind of research ship .
Yeah .
Hey .
The color the mold , it 's different in this cabin .
Yeah .
Look , no eyes .
A good example of ...
mutation caused by radiation .
Maybe this ship was studying the effects of nuclear radiation .
But I wonder why the mold hasn 't covered these shelves too .
Maybe they 're disinfected .
This alcohol lamp 's clean too .
Chemicals seem to stop it .
Uh-huh .
Hey .
Carbolic acid .
If we scrub the cabin with it , we could live here .
That 's right .
What 's this ?
It looks like a giant mushroom , huh ?
Matango .
A kind of mushroom .
It 's probably a new species that was found on this island .
We 're in luck if this thing is edible .
Nothing else written here .
I wonder what happened to all the mirrors ?
Looks like they were taken off .
Hey , let 's go .
The captain 's cabin .
What happened ? !
What is it ? !
Forget it !
Hey , captain 's cabin .
We might be able to find the logbook in here .
Koyama .
Koyama !
What .
What the ...
You-you 're eating !
Who 's that ?
Now , don 't look at us like that .
We found it ...
And it 's first come , first served around here .
Everything seems pretty weird .
We can 't determine the ship 's nationality .
I have the feeling that it 's been deliberately concealed .
The equipments all different .
From communist countries .
From the free world .
From Japan too .
Secret work , huh ?
But involved in some kind of nuclear research .
She certainly wasn 't an ordinary research vessel .
Anyway .
We 'd better figure out what we 're gonna do .
Just a second , though .
Kasai should be here .
Hasn 't he had enough preferential treatment , huh ?
Well , what are you want ?
Hey , Kasai .
All the provisions we 've got ...
won 't last more than a week at this rate .
You can 't stay shut in the room by yourself all the time .
What am I supposed to do ?
We must find a way to live for a month or so ...
we 're talking about that now .
And we think you should come over and discuss it with us .
Oh ...
So you think I 'm wasting my time , huh ?
Well , I 've been cleaning this up .
It 'll come in very handy .
At least we should be able to get some meat .
Yeah , I think this 'll help us stay alive .
Well now , what 's wrong ?
Get on with it .
According to the logbook ...
this island 's deserted .
There 's hardly anything edible on it .
So we 're in a pretty tough spot .
Nevertheless ...
until we can leave here ...
we 've got to eat .
The canned stuff will only last a week .
So we gotta look for food .
Seaweed , fish ...
and turtles eggs .
Anything we can eat ...
including snakes and lizards .
But don 't you even touch the mushrooms .
Why , are they poisonous ?
We don 't know for sure .
There seems to be a substance in them which damages the nerve tissues .
That 's all the records indicate ...
but there 's other evidence .
It 's unlikely that they would have left the ship
permanently as long as they had food .
And we know , from what the log says ...
that every day ...
several men were sent out to gather edibles to add to their diet .
And that none ever returned .
Perhaps this was due to the mushrooms ...
which grow in great abundance on the island .
Now then ...
Better try to move the yacht round to the side , to fix it .
The island is hidden by fog most of the time .
Even if a ship was close ...
we 'd be damn lucky if they spotted us .
So , we 'd better be ready to sail .
Sail again in that yacht ?
Uh-uh ...
I 'm not going .
Maybe you 'll have to !
You won 't get me on it .
You said that we 're near the equator , didn 't you ?
For Japan 's pretty far , and I don 't think that old wreck would make it .
Japan is far away , but I 'm sure we 've been picked up by a ship on the way .
When we 're on a ship , your the skipper ...
so you give the orders ...
and we 're supposed to obey you .
But this isn 't really a ship anymore ...
only a house on land .
Yoshida !
It 's time both of you stopped trying to run things !
What the hell 's the matter with you ?
If you don 't like it , then suppose you tell us what we should do !
Hold it , don 't get angry .
Everyone will have to do their share if we 're going to get out of this .
The women will get the water .
You can go hunting if you like .
Whoever doesn 't work on the boat ...
should make a signal fire on top of one of the mountains .
I will .
- Hello . - Hello , Kasai .
Hi .
How can you write all the time ?
Hmm ?
I 'm certainly glad that I don 't have to work that hard .
I hire people to think for me , and and I just use their thoughts .
Now , that takes talent .
There 's nothing wrong with borrowing talent .
It takes ability .
As well as intelligence .
That 's right .
That 's how civilization progresses ...
by borrowing .
Each generation takes an idea ...
and improves on it .
Novelist do the same thing , don 't they ?
Yeah .
Oh , good evening , sir ... madam .
Your tables over there .
- Hi . - Hi .
- She 's decided to go along with us . - Oh , good .
Thank you very much .
Now ...
here you are .
Here .
We 've been walking all this time and haven 't seen anything yet .
Yeah .
Weren 't all the mirrors on the ship missing ?
These must be the ones .
I wonder why they brought them up here and broke them ?
There must be a reason .
Uh-huh .
What happened ?
Do you think he saw us ?
No .
I think he was afraid of something else .
Hey ...
it 's not so good .
Even the birds don 't want to hang around here .
Sakuta !
Oh ! Another one .
The island is a ship 's graveyard .
Maybe the current ...
It drags them off course .
And they smash themselves against the rocks .
Hi .
Fool !
Don 't call me a fool .
I thought you might be tired so I came to help you .
Give it to me .
Mushrooms .
If you were starving , I 'll bet you 'd take a chance on these , huh ?
- Hey ! - Huh ?
Hey .
Right around here .
Yeah .
I 'm sure I saw something .
Our imagination ?
Come on .
Where are they ?
Not back yet .
Hey !
Blast !
Somebody looked in the window .
Who is it ?
Can 't trust anybody anymore , can you ?
This 'll fix him if he tries it again .
What 's the matter ?
I don 't know , it just went out .
Who 's there ?
- You hear it ? - Yeah .
Koyama !
Yeah .
Was that you ?
No , it wasn 't !
You go up ?
I suppose I need your permission to go to the head ?
Who 's there ? !
It 's me .
What the ?
Did you hear somebody walking on the deck ?
Yeah .
Was it Kasai ?
No !
Help me !
Come here !
Help me ! Come here !
Hey .
Kasai , what happened ?
What happened ?
What 's wrong with you ?
Koyama ! Yoshida ! Get up !
What in the hell 's wrong with you guys ?
In Tokyo ...
you 're all big shots and think you 're pretty smart !
But here you go crazy !
You start seeing ghosts !
You think the ship is haunted !
There 's a reason for all this .
I know what it is .
These women !
They 're on your mind all the time , but you can 't do anything about it .
That 's what 's wrong with everybody , isn 't it ?
Gets me too .
It 's really bugging me .
Tonight ...
I might decide to take her .
Are you going to let him get away with that ?
Nobody 's got guts enough to try and stop me .
Damn you !
I 'll kill you !
Come on !
Stop it !
- Let me go ! - Come on !
That 's enough of that .
Want to know something ?
That broad goes into the jungle with the writer quite a bit .
Seems to me they 're doing more than just carrying water .
Why don 't you mind your own business !
You see ...
she doesn 't deny it , does she ?
I know what kind of a woman she is .
I certainly don 't need you to tell me that .
Okay .
I used you just to get one thing .
Europe is what I wanted , not you .
You 've always been repulsive to me .
What ?
Stop this !
Hey , Koyama ...
are you sure we were seeing ghosts ?
What do you think ?
Come here .
Yoshida , you too !
I suppose that 's imaginary .
Let 's stop fighting each other .
We 've got two things to do .
Get food and fix the yacht so we can get away .
Yeah .
Is that all you 've got to say ?
All you 've done is carry that gun around all day !
And just how much good has that done us ?
- Hey . - Yeah ...
Just let me finish .
There 's a lot of grass growing around here .
You can eat the roots .
You can eat the roots of a lot of plants .
You never thought of that , did you ?
Huh ?
What have you brought back for us ?
You ...
Maybe in Tokyo you 're a clever businessman and make a lot of money .
That isn 't worth a damn here !
Here you gotta work !
So , get to work if you want to eat .
Hey .
College man .
Writer , you too !
You gotta do something , even if it is raining .
What are you waiting for , a miracle ?
Huh ?
Look for food during the day ...
and don 't worry about the rain .
If you were going swimming , you wouldn 't care about it .
You gotta do something !
Akiko .
It 's your mother .
Skipper ...
Even if we fix the yacht , we can 't live long without food .
I 'm gonna go look for some .
What are you looking at ?
What are you doing ?
What 's it look like ?
I wonder who stole the food from us the other night ?
I suppose a ghost stole the key and got into the locker .
Oh , that ...
Too bad I wasn 't able to hold him .
You liar .
Why 'd you try that ?
Showing us the empty cans and claiming ...
some unknown person ate the food .
Huh ?
We didn 't say anything in order to avoid any more arguments .
You 're pretty quick to point out faults and other people .
And ...
you don 't seem to realize those of your own .
I think you 'd better be careful what you say .
What are you gonna do ?
Don 't you worry .
I 'm going after ...
that thing that came on board and frightened everybody .
Yoshida .
Don 't do that .
I 'm sure it was a human being .
Maybe ...
he 's a member of the crew of this ship .
I certainly hope it is a man ...
because then I 'll be able to talk to him .
I 'll be very interested to hear what he says ...
a man thanks strange things when he 's out of his mind .
His reality may be more fascinating than ours .
And it wouldn 't matter what he ate .
Yoshida .
We didn 't get much after working all day .
But we worked hard and we did as much as we could .
You 're right .
Sakuta .
Why don 't you knock before you come in ?
I 'm gonna to take these .
Huh ?
We can 't trust your now .
And you 're gonna sleep and eat with the rest of us !
I don 't sleep very well , except by myself .
You 're going to live and work with the rest of us too !
Damn you .
You depended on me to support your mother and brothers , didn 't you ?
I put you through college and gave you a job in my company !
That 's right .
You pretended to be a friend .
But you always treated me like a dog .
Wonderful .
What do you think of these ?
What kind are they ?
Turtle .
They 're nutritious .
Yeah .
There are 14 .
Two for each .
You don 't get any of these if you 're empty handed .
That doesn 't bother me , I 'm not hungry anymore .
Hey .
Did you eat some of those mushrooms ?
Well ...
that 's a question .
I don 't need anything to eat .
All right , ten thousand each .
Not enough .
No ?
Yesterday it was five thousand .
The market for eggs won 't last forever now , will it ?
All right , two hundred thousand , take it .
It 's a big gamble .
Will I be able to use this or not ?
But I 'll do my damnedest to get off this island .
Even if I have to kill everybody to do it .
So that 's what you 're up to .
Damn you !
- C 'mon now . - Damn you , I 'll fix you .
I 'll cut you up .
Come on .
Sakuta .
Sakuta !
Yeah , I 'm coming .
Stop it !
C 'mon , cut it out !
- Break it up ! - That 's enough of that !
Stop it ! Stop it !
- He had the woman . - Are you jealous of him ? !
We all agree to leave them alone .
You 'd no right to fight him !
Everybody wants me .
I 'll kill you all .
He 's mad .
Yeah .
I ate mushrooms .
Now you know .
I read in a book a long time ago ...
that the Mexicans used to eat them ...
in order to enhance their perception and get a sense of well-being .
Don 't move !
Japanese legends mention laughing mushrooms .
So I 'm in good company .
The people who went out to gather the mushrooms ...
danced in high spirits in the mountains ...
and were in touch with the infinite .
But [ ? ] , according to your understanding ...
it made the person no longer human
That 's just fine by me .
Because when I kill you , I won 't be committing any crime .
I see .
We won 't stand in your way .
Do anything you like !
Oh , I will .
Well ...
truthfully ...
I like Akiko better than the other one .
So , after I 've killed you all ...
- Get him ! - Okay !
The gun !
- Get the gun . - Let go of me .
Get ' em .
Let go .
Why , you dirty ...
I got it !
Stand up !
Okay !
What 's wrong ?
Get in !
Here !
Hey !
What are you doing ?
I told you you 'd have to live with us !
Sakuta !
Looks good !
Good-good job .
You 've worked hard .
Now she 'll sail again .
Did you come to help us ?
Uh-huh , if you want .
But I want to talk to you .
Skipper ...
What do you plan to do now ?
Everything 's different .
Hey , you listening ?
Yeah .
Twenty-four cans of food left .
Not much .
Two people .
Ten days .
Hmm ?
Hey .
How about just the two of us leaving ?
If we had potatoes and seaweed , we can last for a couple of weeks .
There 's plenty of water .
I 'm sure the two of us could stay alive for at least three weeks or so .
We 'd be found by a ship , or maybe hit another island .
Go away !
Okay .
Uh-huh .
The weak restraints of society disintegrate ...
in the face of the will to ...
survive in harsh circumstances .
Man 's power must be turned into creative action .
His reason must grow stronger if we are to continue to progress .
Isn 't there something to eat ?
Kasai , what happened ?
Sakuta !
He stole all the canned food , and left us !
What ?
Dammit !
Dammit .
I guess he didn 't think any of us were worth saving .
In fact , I don 't think he ever had a high opinion of us .
But whatever he thought doesn 't make any difference .
Now it 's my turn to do something .
Mami ...
get the girl over here .
- You dirty ... - No !
Let go !
I 'm gonna kill both of you .
Just start walking down the deck , and don 't try to be heroes .
Murai !
I wonder how many times I 've ...
written something like this in my novels ?
Oh , Koyama .
Give me that ...
that gun !
So , go eat mushrooms !
You too !
Go !
Oh , please !
You said you preferred him , didn 't ya ?
Well , go with him !
I 'll bet this didn 't happen in your filthy novels !
Stop it !
It 's been raining for a whole week now .
It must be the rainy season .
Well , if you 're right ...
we won 't be able to live here very long .
Do you know anywhere else we can go ?
We 'll have to find a place .
Maybe we can find a cave .
Murai ...
I 'm finished .
No more .
Kasai ...
No matter how we feel , we can 't give up !
You just can 't sit there and do nothing .
Oh , stop it !
I wish ...
you 'd kill me .
I ...
I don 't even have the courage to kill myself !
I didn 't even hear you .
You take a rest .
That 's a good idea .
You take it easy , and we 'll bring you something to eat .
We 'll be okay ...
and so will you .
Let 's go .
Mami .
You 're-you 're still alive .
How did you do it , huh ?
I haven 't been hungry since I left .
Mami .
Oh , help me .
Help me .
I 've waited a long time to hear you say that .
It was worth it .
Now you finally know what it means to ask for help .
I 'll help you .
Come with me .
The mushrooms have grown since the rains came .
Aren 't we lucky .
When can we eat ?
Soon .
Follow me .
It 's delicious .
We should have eaten them sooner .
I didn 't tell you that once you 've eaten it ...
you become a mushroom too .
That was was why all the men ...
took the mirrors off the ship , you see .
And once you start you can 't stop .
Yoshida .
Kasai !
Kasai .
Kasai ?
Kasai !
No .
Can 't , I can 't .
Take it easy .
Stop crying .
Hey !
Over here !
Sakuta .
Sakuta !
M. Kasai .
K. Murai .
E. Yoshida .
S. Koyama .
Mami Sekiguchi .
Miss Soma .
These people were cast ashore on a deserted island , and died .
I tried to escape and reach help ...
but I couldn 't make it ...
and I died in the sea .
N. Sakuta ...
Captain .
Dammit !
The yacht came back .
Huh ?
The yacht .
Sakuta came back for us ?
Sakuta died at sea .
The yacht drifted back .
So then ...
we 'll never be able to get off this island , will we ?
Is this all you could find today ?
And I haven 't had any .
Hey ...
can 't we eat the mushrooms now ?
That would really be the end of us .
But ...
Mami and Kasai ...
Fool !
They 're half mushroom .
So what ?
If we can 't get off this island ...
maybe there 's no other way to live , so ...
I might be wrong .
I wish I could learn to live like you .
I 'm not good !
No good at all .
I wish I could kill myself .
Akiko .
I must tell you that I 'm in love with you .
Oh , darling !
Take it easy .
We 'll make it .
Hey ...
I 'll spend the day getting as much food as possible .
Then we 'll get on the yacht .
Murai !
Akiko !
Akiko .
Murai !
Akiko ?
Akiko !
Murai .
Akiko .
It 's delicious .
Really .
Fool !
Come on !
Dammit !
Murai .
Then the night game .
And the morning came .
And then the night came again .
I hardly remember when I was rescued .
However , I 'm sorry now that I was .
If I was really in love with her ...
I should 've eaten the mushrooms with her , and ...
and become one .
At least we would have been together .
But I came back ...
only to be condemned as insane .
I had no choice ...
all that time ...
oh , we suffered ...
with hunger , and ...
And then I lost her , I was confused ...
I couldn 't decide ...
what to do , and ..
and then ...
I ate them !
Here , now ...
You should consider yourself fortunate ...
that someone finally found you .
Do you think so ?
Tokyo is not very different from that island .
People in cities are cruel , aren 't they ?
It 's all the same ...
I would be happier living on that island ...
than in this city !